<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[ELIF] SRTS - Helicopters (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ELIFSRTSHelicopters</packageId>
  <author>ELIF</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ELIFSRTSHelicopters</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>Shashlichnik.srtsexpanded</packageId>
      <displayName>SRTS Expanded</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2938738526</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Shashlichnik.srtsexpanded</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://img.litet.net/logos/Info.png[/img]
Update of ELIFs mod https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2575097304
with permission

[img]https://img.litet.net/logos/Notice.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr][td][url=https://discord.gg/h5TY6DA][img]https://img.litet.net/logos/Discord.png[/img][/url][/td] [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/ELIFSRTSHelicopters][img]https://img.litet.net/logos/Github.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://img.litet.net/logos/SafeToAdd.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://img.litet.net/logos/RemoveMayWork.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://img.litet.net/logos/OriginalDescription.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/pfYRQLU.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/jYTDrpK.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/QJuhovd.png[/img]
Ever wanted to fly through Rimworld with style and practicality? Well, helicopters are here to bring you just that, helicopters have always been the king when it comes to aeronautical utility, the ability for helicopters to land without a runway is incredibly useful, especially when secure spaces are of a premium due to pesky raiders trying to steal your tables, it also allows you to launch attack operations without needing an entire airfield to land on, which is great for retaliation and retaking your stolen tables.
[url=https://www.reddit.com/r/ukraine/comments/s6g5un/want_to_support_ukraine_heres_a_list_of_charities/][img]https://img.litet.net/lLqexL2.png[/img][/url]
[img]https://img.litet.net/uHB4Uql.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/Tn3fCyc.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/s275khk.gif[/img]
We present to you, proper spinning top and tail propellers, for your eyes to consume, each helicopter has its own unique propeller, they ramp up during loading for takeoff and ramp down after landing as you would expect, and the rotors don’t spin when it’s not fueled, giving it that small sense of polish.

[img]https://img.litet.net/vINdkpm.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/lC130S4.gif[/img]
And of course, Helicopters also throw out a bunch of dust and dirt because of its high-speed upside-down lawn mower blades, so we made it so that dust effects will be emitted whenever the rotors are spinning, which gives it little bit of visual flavor.

[img]https://img.litet.net/vuo1PhF.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/mvB9IQK.png[/img]
By the time you reach late game, specialized helicopters should become more appealing for you, we have designed 4 helicopters for 4 specific use cases, strategic bombing, fast deploy extra-long-range transport, a huge capacity but slow transport, and a fuel-hungry huge capacity fast transport.

[img]https://img.litet.net/QPbnhX1.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/kFFgZ8T.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/vcC31dH.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/WFo1BaV.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/7SI7BNy.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/FQ0d7yY.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/j3m7MUM.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/fN0jSlA.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/ainrytf.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/7VBnffP.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/tMGBu5U.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/yHvCOI3.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/vFKUHGg.png[/img]
Are you looking for a translation? Well, here’s a list of available translations that have been published in the workshop for this mod (Note: we are not responsible for any inaccuracy in the following list of translations).

Did you make a translation and want it to be shown on this list for people to easily find? Just post the link to your translation down in the comments and we’ll add it to the list.
[b]Available Translations:[/b]
[list]
[*][b][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2587715763]Chinese/个人简中汉化 Translation[/url][/b] – by [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198057623118]waghhhhhhhhhhhh[/url]
[*][b][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2915047654]Russian/русский Translation[/url][/b] – by [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/mcdeimos]Деймос[/url]
[*][b][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2829741197]Japanese/日本 Translation[/url][/b] – by [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198137061139]ジード[/url]
[/list]
[img]https://img.litet.net/3lMgEhC.png[/img]
If you happen to notice any incompatibilities or partial incompatibilities, feel free to inform us so we can inform and warn other users of possible incompatibilities with other mods.
[b]Compatibility list:[/b]
[list]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2812930163][b][DHM] AIRDOCK[/b][/url] – The author has provided support for this mod so you can create a deep storage solution for SRTS vehicles, allowing you to store multiple SRTS vehicles in one area.
[/list]
[b]Partial Incompatibility list:[/b]
[list]
[*][b]Combat Extended[/b] – Transport jobs work fine, bombing outright does not work.
[/list]
[b]Incompatibility list:[/b]
[list]
[*]None at this moment
[/list]

[img]https://img.litet.net/fpb3Xl7.png[/img]
[img]https://img.litet.net/uTWUxKc.png[/img]
[b]Q:[/b] I can't seem to find where I can build the helicopter after researching it?
[b]A:[/b] Make sure SRTS is loaded first before this mod.

[b]Q:[/b] What's the difference between Precision Run Cap and Bombing Run Cap?
[b]A:[/b] Precision Run Cap is how many bombs the helicopter will drop during Precision runs, while Bombing Run Capacity is how many bombs it will carpet bomb during Bombing runs.

[b]Q:[/b] Can I add this mod mid-save?
[b]A:[/b] There shouldn't be an issue with adding this mod mid-save.

[b]Q:[/b] Can I remove this mod mid-save?
[b]A:[/b] We do not recommend removing mods mid-save, but if you really want to, it should be fine.

[b]Q:[/b] Why isn't my helicopter dropping bombs?
[b]A:[/b] The helicopter uses mortar shells in its inventory to bomb, so make sure to load the helicopter with the appropriate shell you wish to use.

[b]Q:[/b] Can I suggest a helicopter?
[b]A:[/b] Sure, but do not expect a reply or an acknowledgment, we’ll think about it, but with my busy schedule, and other projects I plan to make, it might not be feasible.

[b]Q:[/b] Can I create translations/localizations for your mods?
[b]A:[/b] Sure, in fact, we welcome translations from other users, simply inform us down in the comments and we’ll put a link to your translation on the workshop above, so people can easily find them.

[b]Q:[/b] Do you plan on porting this to Phil’s Vehicle Framework?
[b]A:[/b] Yes! Once it's released, we will immediately try to port this to Phil’s Vehicle Framework, along with some changes and improvements to make use of the new features of Phil’s Vehicle Framework.

[img]https://img.litet.net/logos/ReportingIssues.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Always post your log using the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Log Uploader[/url]
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list] 

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/3732934346][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/ELIFSRTSHelicopters?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url] | tags: aircraft, transport</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.6.1</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>